Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Ooh!
♪ 哦！
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ Spongebob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ Spongebob
Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ Spongebob Squarepants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ Spongebob Squarepants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ Spongebob Squarepants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
[Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
[字幕由THE赞助
美国教育部
[and NICKELODEON]
[和尼克频道]
Oh!
哦！
Pardon me, young lady.
请原谅我，年轻的女士。
What a fox.
真是一只狐狸啊。
Ooh!
哦！
You're all mine,
you sweet Krabby Patty.
你都是我的
你可爱的蟹蟹帕蒂。
Ooh, whoo!
哦，呼！
Initiating launch sequence.
启动启动序列。
Krabby Patty, here I come!
克拉比帕蒂，我来了！
Eh, I hope I don't miss again.
嗯，希望不要再错过了。
Reunited, and it's going
to feel so good!
重逢，一切都会过去
感觉真好！
Oh, ho, ho, sweet wampum.
哦，嗬，嗬，甜甜的贝壳。
Huh?! What's that?!
啊？！那是什么？
Squidward, where are you?!
章鱼哥，你在哪里？！
Shield me with your forehead!
用你的额头保护我！
So...
所以...
it was just another failed
Krabby Patty theft attempt
这只是又一次失败
克拉比帕蒂盗窃未遂
by my arch-competitor, Plankton.
由我的主要竞争对手 Plankton 提供。
For a second there,
I mistook you for a threat
有那么一秒钟，
我误以为你是威胁
but you're just
a dirty, little man.
但你只是
一个肮脏的小男人。
So long, shrimp!
久违了，虾！
Curse you, Mr. Krabs!
诅咒你，蟹老板！
Ouch!
哎哟!
So, typical day of failure,
I see, huh, darling?
所以，典型的失败日，
我明白了，嗯，亲爱的？
Oh, can it, computer wife.
哦，可以吗，电脑老婆。
Can't you see I'm exhausted?
你没看到我已经筋疲力尽了吗？
Why don't you go
make yourself useful
你为什么不走
让自己变得有用
and synthesize me up some grub?
并为我合成一些食物？
Yes, Your Majesty.
是的，陛下。
What do we got here?
我们在这里得到了什么？
Oh, goodie!
哦，好家伙！
Holographic meatloaf again.
又是全息肉饼。
When am I going to get
some realfood?
我什么时候才能得到
一些真正的食物？
Mr. Krabs gets to eat real food.
蟹老板可以吃到真正的食物了。
Just look at his daughter.
只要看看他的女儿就知道了。
She's as big as a whale.
她像鲸鱼一样大。
I wish I could be successful
like Mr. Krabs.
我希望我能成功
就像蟹老板一样。
I wish I could somehow
just switch lives with him
我希望我能以某种方式
只是和他交换生活
just to know what it's like.
只是想知道那是什么样子。
Then why don't you just use
那你为什么不直接使用
that Switch-Lives-Just-to-Know-
What-It's-Like-O-Macrofier thing
那开关-活着-只是为了知道-
O-Macrofier 是什么样的东西
you built last Tuesday?
你上周二建的吗？
What a brilliant idea!
多么绝妙的主意啊！
Your parents
must have been, like
你的父母
一定是，就像
part computer or something.
部分计算机或其他东西。
Ah...
啊...
Now, let's see here.
现在，让我们看看这里。
No.
不。
Aha!
啊哈！
Well, I hate to leave you, Karen
好吧，我不想离开你，凯伦
but you know what they say:
但你知道他们怎么说：
"a rolling stone gathers
no algae."
“滚石聚集
没有藻类。”
Ah!
啊!
Oh, dear Neptune above!
哦，上面亲爱的海王星！
What happened last night?
昨晚发生了什么？
Huh?
啊？
What's this?
这是什么？
"Mr.Plankton"?
“浮游生物先生”？
Who the davey...?
戴维是谁……？
Huh? I'm in the Krusty Krab.
啊？我在蟹堡王里。
And that means the life switcher
这意味着生活的切换者
was a success!
很成功！
The Krusty Krab is mine!
蟹堡王是我的了！
Corporate casual.
商务休闲。
Order up!
赶快下单吧！
Two deluxe Krabby Patties.
两份豪华蟹肉饼。
At last!
终于！
There you are, sir.
就在这儿，先生。
Two deluxe...
两间豪华...
Ahoy, there,
Mr. Plankton.
哎哟，那里，
浮游生物先生。
Er, uh, hey, there,
uh, Spongebob.
呃，呃，嘿，那里，
呃，海绵宝宝。
Uh, Spongebob...
呃，海绵宝宝...
Yes, sir?
是吗，先生？
I'm going to need
to take one of these patties
我需要
拿一块肉饼
back to my office
for, uh... bun inspection.
回到我的办公室
用于，呃...包子检查。
I'm afraid you can't do that
恐怕你做不到
Mr. Plankton.
浮游生物先生。
But why not?
但为什么不呢？
Because that patty is
for the customer, sir.
因为那个馅饼是
为了客户，先生。
The customer?
客户？
I'll boil the customer
in hot oil
我来煮顾客
在热油中
and I'll rip out his...!
我会撕掉他的……！
I mean, yes, of course,
for the lovely customer.
我的意思是，是的，当然，
为了可爱的顾客。
But you can
take these
patties, sir.
但你可以
拿这些
馅饼，先生。
I made them on the off chance
我偶然做了它们
you decided to instigate
你决定煽动
some bun inspection
today, Mr. Plankton, sir.
一些包子检查
今天，浮游生物先生，先生。
Uh, yes.
Uh, very nice.
呃，是的。
呃，非常好。
Um, thanks.
嗯，谢谢。
All mine!
都是我的！
It's finally all mine!
终于都是我的了！
The patties...
肉饼...
the wealth...
财富...
the notoriety...
恶名...
the... Spongebob?
海绵宝宝？
What do you want?
你想要什么？
Well, it's just that
it's Tuesday again, sir
嗯，仅此而已
又到了星期二，先生
and I was wondering
if I could have my...
我想知道
如果我能拥有我的...
uh... my, uh...
呃……我的，呃……
weekly performance review.
每周绩效评估。
Review?
审查？
Oh, yes, please, sir, please!
噢，是的，求你了，先生，求你了！
But I've never reviewed
anything...
但我从来没有评论过
任何...
except for those foreign
exercise videos
除了那些外国的
锻炼视频
my cousin sent me.
我表弟发给我的。
Oh, please, sir!
哦，拜托，先生！
I want to make you
so happy and proud!
我想让你
如此高兴和自豪！
Ah, you're doing fine.
啊，你做得很好。
Now leave me to my work.
现在让我继续工作吧。
Mmm...
嗯...
But sir...
但是先生...
I thought I sent
you away, Cretan!
我以为我发送了
你走开，克里特岛！
But sir, there's got to be
something I need to improve on.
但是先生，一定有
我需要改进的地方。
Anything!
任何事物！
All right, the sauce.
好吧，酱汁。
Wh... what?
什...什么？
The sauce, I don't know.
酱汁我不知道。
You're using
too much sauce, okay?
你正在使用
酱太多了好吗？
Review's over.
审核完毕。
What?
什么？
What's the matter with you?
你怎么了？
All I said was
a little too much sauce.
我所说的只是
酱汁有点太多了。
It's no big deal, really.
这没什么大不了的，真的。
What do you want from me,
a promotion?
你想从我这里得到什么
促销？
A pro... a promot...
a promotion?!
专业人士……晋升……
促销？！
Uh, sure, kid, you're, uh...
呃，当然，孩子，你是，呃...
you're on register now.
您现在正在注册。
Register?
登记？
Glad that's over.
很高兴一切都结束了。
Spongebob, do you remember
that little talk we had
海绵宝宝你还记得吗
我们的闲聊
about personal space?
关于个人空间？
It's okay, Squidward,
I'm official. Look!
没关系，章鱼哥
我是官方的。看！
Co-cashier?!
副收银员？！
So, have you two
known each other long?
那么，你们两个
认识多久了？
You can't do this to me,
Mr. Plankton!
你不能这样对我
浮游生物先生！
If you think I'm going
to stand out there all day
如果你认为我会去
整天站在那里
listening to...
听...
then you must have coral
wedged in your frontal lobe!
那你一定有珊瑚
楔入你的额叶！
So what do you want me to do
about it?
那你想让我做什么
关于它？
I'd like my view
to be a little less yellow
我想要我的观点
颜色不要那么黄
if you know what I mean.
如果你明白我的意思。
Hope you like gray.
希望你喜欢灰色。
Hey, Squidward, I can see you
through this little window.
嘿，章鱼哥，我能看见你
透过这个小窗。
Now, no more intrusions.
现在，不再有任何入侵。
I'd like to begin writing
the memoirs of my success story.
我想开始写作
我的成功故事的回忆录。
So everyone just stay the...
所以大家就呆在...
Daddy!
爸爸！
Daddy! Daddy, Daddy,
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy!
爸爸！爸爸，爸爸，
爸爸，爸爸，爸爸！
Just tell Daddy what you want!
只要告诉爸爸你想要什么就可以了！
Daddy!
爸爸！
He's very busy!
他很忙！
Could I please have a, um...
an advance on my allowance?
我可以请一个，嗯...
预支我的津贴？
If it'll get you
out of my antennae.
如果它能得到你
从我的触角里出来。
Go crazy.
发疯吧。
One dollar!
一美元！
You hateme!
你恨我！
Ow!
噢！
You!
你！
Me?
我？
You think this is funny?
你觉得这很有趣吗？
In a cosmic sort of way, yes.
从宇宙的角度来看，是的。
Well, Mr. Funny Man
嗯，有趣的人先生
is this how you get
your sick kicks?!
这就是你得到的
你有病吗？！
What? It's just
an ordinary Krabby...
什么？这只是
一只普通的蟹...
Oh, my goodness!
哦，我的天啊！
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
I tried,
Mr. Plankton.
我尝试过，
浮游生物先生。
I really did.
我真的做到了。
Oh, what now?
哦，现在怎么办？
A customer ordered a medium soda
一位顾客点了一杯中杯苏打水
and I gave him a large.
我给了他一个大的。
I gave him a large!
我给了他一个大的！
I've soiled
the good Krusty Krab name!
我弄脏了
蟹堡王的好名字！
Soiled it! Soiled it...!
弄脏了！弄脏了……！
I command you to stop that.
我命令你停止这样做。
Stop that, and return
to your post!
停下来，然后返回
到你的帖子！
Soiled it!
Soiled it...!
弄脏了！
弄脏了……！
Where's the off button
on this thing?
关闭按钮在哪里
在这件事上？
Okay, Daddy, I've decided
I'm going to run away.
好吧，爸爸，我决定了
我要逃跑。
Run away and find a newdaddy!
赶紧逃走，去找个新爸爸吧！
Make it stop!
让它停下来！
What, did I say the secret word?
什么，我说了密语了吗？
No, sir.
不，先生。
He's back.
他回来了。
Who's back? What?
谁回来了？什么？
What was that?!
那是什么？
Man your stations!
Red alert! Red alert!
管理你的车站！
红色警报！红色警报！
Take cover!
掩护！
Take cover from what?!
躲避什么？！
He's around here somewhere.
他就在这附近的某个地方。
There he goes!
他走了！
What? Who? Where?
什么？ WHO？在哪里？
Somebody tell me!
有人告诉我吗！
Some say he crawled out
有人说他是爬出来的
from the lowest trench
in the ocean.
从最低的沟渠
在海洋中。
He's the saltiest
of all of the sea dogs.
他是最咸的
所有的海狗。
He's the most hated creature
in Bikini Bottom.
他是最让人讨厌的生物
在比基尼底部。
And he's finally got
a Krabby Patty!
而他终于得到了
蟹肉饼！
Krabs?! What the barnacle
is going on here?!
螃蟹？！什么藤壶
这是怎么回事？！
It's your arch-competitor...
Krabs!
这是你的主要竞争对手...
螃蟹们！
His goal in life
is to steal a Krabby Patty
他的人生目标
就是偷一个蟹肉饼
and ruin our restaurant.
并毁了我们的餐厅。
That's terrible!
太可怕了！
Yeah! But the worst part
of it is...
是的！但最糟糕的部分
其中...
Good grief, he's naked!
天哪，他赤身裸体！
Clothe me if you can,
silly landlubbers!
如果可以的话给我穿衣服
愚蠢的旱鸭子！
I'm going to make you
eat those words, Krabs!
我要让你
吃掉这些话吧，螃蟹们！
No shirt, no shoes...
no service!
没穿衬衫，没穿鞋子……
没有服务！
Huh?!
啊？！
Ah, you got me!
啊，你抓住了我！
Well, at least it's underwire.
好吧，至少它是有钢圈的。
Here's your stinking patty!
这是你的臭肉饼！
I don't understand.
我不明白。
Is there a gas leak in here?
这里有煤气泄漏吗？
Knick-knack, the patty's back.
小窍门，馅饼回来了。
You did it, Mr. Plankton.
你做到了，浮游生物先生。
Victory screech!
胜利的尖叫！
Enjoy your victory screech,
Plankton
享受你胜利的尖叫，
浮游生物
because someday the Krabby Patty
formula will be mine!
因为有一天蟹肉饼
公式将是我的！
You'll never get this formula
你永远不会得到这个公式
you twisted fiend!
你这个扭曲的恶魔！
Oh, but I will!
哦，但我会的！
Even if I have
to come back tomorrow
即使我有
明天回来
and the next day
和第二天
and the next day next day
以及后天 后天
and the next day
和第二天
and the next day...
然后第二天...
Phone call,
Mr. Plankton.
电话，
浮游生物先生。
The next day, and the next day
后天，后天
and the next day
and the next day...
和第二天
然后第二天...
It's not worth it!
这不值得！
It's just not worth it!
这根本不值得！
Good-bye, everyone.
再见，大家。
I'll remember you all
in therapy.
我会记住你们所有人
在治疗中。
Holographic meatloaf...
全息肉饼...
my favorite!
我最喜欢的！
Ah! Goo Lagoon...
啊!古泻湖...
where the sun is hot
太阳很热的地方
and the sunbathers
和日光浴者
are oh, so cool.
哦，太酷了。
What a beautiful day.
多么美好的一天啊。
You said it, pal.
你说过了，朋友。
Can you believe that sun?
你能相信那个太阳吗？
I could look at it all day.
我可以看一整天。
Uh, Patrick?
呃，帕特里克？
What?
什么？
Nothing.
没有什么。
So, how's that tan coming?
那么，晒黑是怎么来的呢？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Let me check.
让我检查一下。
Looking good.
看起来不错。
How's yours?
你的怎么样？
Just a minute.
请等一下。
I could have sworn
I was laying on my back.
我本可以发誓
我仰面躺着。
Larry! Larry!
拉里！拉里！
Hey, it's Larry, the lifeguard.
嘿，我是救生员拉里。
Mr. Lifeguard,
can I feel
your muscle?
救生员先生，
我能感觉到吗
你的肌肉？
Sure. Don't scratch
the paint.
当然。不要抓伤
油漆。
Lifeguard, how's the tubage?
救生员，管子怎么样？
Gnarly, dudes.
粗俗，伙计们。
All right, yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
好吧，是啊！
呼呼！
Lifeguard, can
you point out
the snack bar?
救生员可以
你指出
小吃店？
Right over there.
就在那里。
But you guys are way too old
但你们已经太老了
and unsightly for my beach.
而且对我的海滩来说也不美观。
And I'm afraid I'm going
to have to ask you to leave.
我恐怕我要走了
不得不请你离开。
So polite.
很有礼貌。
Just like we raised him.
就像我们抚养他一样。
What a guy.
真是个家伙啊。
Is it any wonder
he's so popular?
有什么奇怪的吗
他这么受欢迎？
Just imagine
if Iwere a lifeguard.
想象一下
假如我是一名救生员。
That would be so cool.
那真是太酷了。
Oh, what do you want
to be a lifeguard for?
哦，你想要什么
成为一名救生员？
Nobody really likes those guys.
没有人真正喜欢这些家伙。
For he's a jolly, good fellow...
因为他是一个快乐的好人...
Being a lifeguard is so dumb.
当救生员真是太愚蠢了。
All they do is blow, blow,
blow on their stupid whistles
他们所做的就是吹，吹，
吹响他们愚蠢的口哨
rub, rub, rub that white stuff
on their noses
擦擦擦那个白色的东西
在他们的鼻子上
and show off their gross
并炫耀他们的毛病
misshapen bodies.
畸形的身体。
Dude, put that thing away.
伙计，把那东西收起来。
There are, like, children here.
这里有，比如，孩子。
I'm going to the snack bar.
我要去小吃店。
Who needs to be a lifeguard?
谁需要成为救生员？
I'm cool.
我很酷。
I'm every bit as cool as Larry.
我和拉里一样酷。
And if I'm not,
let me be struck by...
如果我不是，
让我震惊...
A flying ice cream truck...
会飞的冰淇淋车...
and live!
并生活！
Please, do not land
请不要着陆
flying ice cream trucks
on the bathers.
飞行冰淇淋车
在沐浴者身上。
Oh...
哦...
Spongebob, you okay?
海绵宝宝，你还好吗？
Hey!
嘿！
I didn't know
you were a lifeguard.
我不知道
你是一名救生员。
Lifeguard?
救生员？
The nose.
鼻子。
White stuff.
白色的东西。
You think I'm a lifeguard?
你以为我是救生员吗？
Sure, there's no hiding
the lifeguard look, Spongebob
当然，没有什么可隐藏的
救生员的样子，海绵宝宝
and you've got it.
你已经得到它了。
You really think so?
你真的这么认为吗？
You bet, I do.
你敢打赌，我愿意。
Say, we're a little
shorthanded around here.
说吧，我们还小
这里人手短缺。
How would you like
to work the beach?
你想要怎样
去海滩工作？
I'd love it!
我会喜欢的！
All right.
好的。
Leave that on the bench, Kahuna.
把它放在板凳上，卡胡纳。
Hey, Annette, come here.
嘿，安妮特，过来。
I want you to meet
my buddy, Spongebob.
我想让你见见
我的好朋友，海绵宝宝。
Hi.
你好。
Hey, guy's a lifeguard.
嘿，这家伙是救生员。
It works.
有用。
Whoo-hoo!
呼呼！
That was the greatest, Larry.
那是最伟大的，拉里。
Yeah.
是的。
Say, how'd you like to take
the second shift?
说吧，你想采取什么方式
第二班？
By myself?
靠我自己吗？
Only if you think you're ready.
仅当您认为自己已经准备好时。
I'm not just ready.
我还没有准备好。
I'm Ready Freddie.
我准备好了，弗雷迪。
It's Larry.
是拉里。
Well, I guess I'll just...
好吧，我想我只会...
Help! Help!
帮助！帮助！
Help!
帮助！
Help! help!
帮助！帮助！
We've got a sinker.
我们有一个沉降片。
Spongebob, let me take this.
海绵宝宝，让我拿走这个。
I haven't seen
any action all day.
我没见过
一整天的任何行动。
Action?
行动？
Please, help.
请帮忙。
Breathe, darn you!
呼吸，该死的你！
That's the last time
I read and swim.
这是最后一次
我读书和游泳。
You saved my life.
你救了我的命。
Don't mention it.
It's all part of the job.
别提了。
这都是工作的一部分。
You know, Spongebob, the babes
你知道，海绵宝宝，宝贝们
and the big chair are great
和大椅子很棒
but the best part is knowing
you're the only thing
但最好的部分是知道
你是唯一的东西
that stands between
these good people...
介于
这些好人...
Go, go, go, go, go...
走，走，走，走，走……
and a watery grave.
和一个水坟墓。
And that's what it's all about.
这就是全部内容。
Their lives are
in your hands now
他们的生活是
现在在你手中
'cause I got a date
with a tanning booth.
因为我有个约会
配有晒黑亭。
See you.
再见。
But I...
但我...
can't swim.
不会游泳。
Oh, if I'd known
being a lifeguard meant
哦，如果我知道的话
成为一名救生员意味着
guarding their lives,
I would never have said yes.
守护着他们的生命，
我永远不会答应。
Maybe nothing will go wrong.
也许什么都不会出错。
Then when Larry comes back
然后当拉里回来时
I'll tell him
I'm not interested.
我会告诉他
我不感兴趣。
Besides, what's the worst
that could happen?
除此之外，最糟糕的是什么
这可能发生吗？
Emergency!
Everybody out of the water.
紧急情况！
大家都从水里出来了。
Hurry! Emergency!
Out of the water.
匆忙！紧急情况！
从水里出来。
Emergency!
紧急情况！
What's going on, lifeguard?
救生员，怎么了？
What's the big emergency?
有什么大紧急情况？
Uh... there are
sharks in there.
呃……有
里面有鲨鱼。
Hey, that's my family
you're talking about.
嘿，那是我的家人
你说的是。
A... sea monster!
一只……海怪！
You know, we sea monsters
have made great strides
你知道，我们是海怪
取得了长足的进步
in the fields of science
and literature.
在科学领域
和文学。
Uh... somebody went?
呃……有人去了吗？
It's a big lagoon, dude.
这是一个大泻湖，伙计。
Disgusting!
恶心！
No, don't go!
不，别走！
Free ice cream!
免费冰淇淋！
Plenty for everybody.
适合每个人。
One for you, one for you...
一份给你，一份给你……
Okay, everybody got one?
好吧，每个人都有一个吗？
Mmm, yeah!
嗯，是啊！
Mmm...
嗯...
Aha, now I got you.
啊哈，现在我找到你了。
Now, you all have to wait
one hour before you go swimming.
现在，大家必须等待
去游泳前一小时。
But just so you're not tempted.
但只是为了让你不受诱惑。
Ladies and gentlemen
女士们，先生们
the lagoon is closed.
泻湖已关闭。
We like Larry better.
我们更喜欢拉里。
Does Larry ever give you
free ice cream?
拉里有给过你吗
免费冰淇淋？
Ice cream!
冰淇淋！
Did somebody say, "ice cream?"
有人说“冰淇淋吗？”
Where is it?
它在哪里？
Is it here?
是这里吗？
Huh?
啊？
Ice cream! Yay!
冰淇淋！耶！
Cramp!
抽筋！
Oh!
哦！
Holy cow!
圣牛！
Somebody's drowning!
有人溺水了！
Oh, no, that's not possible.
哦，不，那不可能。
The lagoon is closed.
泻湖已关闭。
Dude, get your butt
in the water.
哥们，放开你的屁股
在水中。
If there was anyone in there,
we'd hear them.
如果里面有人的话
我们会听到他们的声音。
Help, help!
救命，救命！
I can't swim!
我不会游泳！
Somebody would be screaming
that they're drowning...
有人会尖叫
他们快要淹死了……
I'm drowning!
我快淹死了！
They would have to have
crossed the line.
他们必须有
越线了。
I'm drowning
'cause I crossed the line.
我快淹死了
因为我越界了。
Okay, I'll take a look...
好的，我去看看...
but just to prove to you that...
Patrick isn't drowning!
但只是为了向你证明...
帕特里克没有溺水！
Can't swim!
不会游泳！
Butt hurts.
屁股疼。
Ice cream.
冰淇淋。
Hold on, Patrick.
坚持住，帕特里克。
I'm coming.
我来了。
Help, help!
救命，救命！
Don't move.
别动。
Catch this.
抓住这个。
Quit fooling around, man.
Get in the water.
别再胡闹了，伙计。
进入水中。
Help, help!
救命，救命！
Oh, what am I going to do?
Got to think.
哦，我该怎么办？
必须想一想。
Got to think.
Got to run around and think.
必须想一想。
必须跑来跑去思考。
Got to run around
and think at the same time.
得四处奔波
同时思考。
Got to think,
got to have a plan.
必须想一想，
必须有一个计划。
Got to think, think, think.
I've got it!
必须思考、思考、思考。
我明白了！
Patrick can't drown
if there isn't any water.
帕特里克不会被淹死
如果没有水的话。
Well, you're safe now, Patrick.
好吧，你现在安全了，帕特里克。
Help, I'm drowning,
I've got butt cramps
救命啊我快淹死了
我屁股抽筋
I want ice cream
and now it's dark.
我想要冰淇淋
现在天黑了。
Help, help!
Help me, I'm drowning.
救命，救命！
救救我，我快淹死了。
Help.
帮助。
To us.
对我们来说。
Oh!
哦！
Sorry.
Here's your hot dog.
对不起。
这是你的热狗。
Okay, Patrick, here I come.
好吧，帕特里克，我来了。
Oh.
哦。
Come, come 'round Pat.
来吧，过来帕特。
Here I am.
我在这里。
Pat, Pat, no.
Uncle, hold it,
Pat, Pat, stop.
帕特，帕特，不。
大叔，坚持住
帕特，帕特，停下来。
No, Pat, stop.
不，帕特，停下来。
Stop, stop!
停下来，停下来！
Oh. Sorry.
哦。对不起。
Help! Help!
帮助！帮助！
Save me, can't swim.
救救我，我不会游泳。
Patrick, don't.
帕特里克，别这样。
Help.
帮助。
Help, help, help...
救命，救命，救命……
Help!
帮助！
Help us.
We're drowning!
帮助我们。
我们快淹死了！
I wonder what's showing
我想知道正在显示什么
at the movie theater
right about now.
在电影院
就现在。
Good-bye, Patrick.
再见，帕特里克。
Good-bye, ice cream.
再见，冰淇淋。
Help, can't swim. Help, can't swim.
救命，不会游泳。救命，不会游泳。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
哦，不。哦，不。
Spongebob?
海绵宝宝？
Yes, Larry?
是的，拉里？
You're not a lifeguard, are you?
你不是救生员，是吗？
No, Larry.
不，拉里。
Let's go, guys.
我们走吧，伙计们。
Very good.
非常好。
You fellows are learning fast.
你们学得很快。
Ow!
噢！
Butt cramps! Butt cramps!
屁股抽筋！屁股抽筋！
And I still don't
have my ice cream.
而我还是不
吃我的冰淇淋吧。
And NICKELODEON
还有尼克罗迪恩
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
[标题为
字幕中心
WGBH教育基金会]
[标题为
字幕中心
WGBH教育基金会]